skills
hobbies
contact me
Ukraine, Dnipro
• <u>+380 957 357 197</u>
uyriparaka@gmail.com
GitHub Freelance
About me
Hello, I'm Yurii Paraka. I am a beginner web developer. I started to get involved in web development as a leisure activity half a year ago, and after a while I realized that I really like web development and I decided to change the type of my activity. Now I am actively studying in this direction and I really like it. I am 29 years old, I live, study and work in the city of Dnipro.
work experience
• Freelance
Nov 2021 - Today
Web developer
Novice freelancer. Working with novice designers in a team on the development of the first commercial projects
Selfeducation
Sep 2021 - Today

About myWork experienceEducationPortfolio

contact medonwload cv

Paraka Yurii

front-end developer

## Student

Independent study of materials on Internet resources. Also courses on training platforms Udemy. Analysis of existing sites. Development and writing of your own projects.

## education

"National Mining University"
 Bachelor's Degree

2010 - 2014

speciality: " Automobiles and Automobile economy "

qualification: " Specialist in road transport " (" Transport engineer ")

• " National Mining University "

Specialist Degree

2014 - 2015

speciality: " Automobiles and Automobile economy "

qualification: " Expert in road transport " (" Transport engineer ")

• " National Mining University "

Master's Degree

2015 - 2016

speciality: "Business Economics "

qualification: " Master of Finance "

## **Portfolio**

go to site

Hello:)

© 2021 Paraka Yurii